Guide to the Administrative Files of the Dean of the School of Education, Daniel E. Griffiths 1948-1985 (Bulk 1965-1983) RG 26.0.1 RG.26.0.1
New York University Archives
- Griffiths Container List
  - Hindel Committee Report, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - IDS Institute for Developmental Studies, 1979-1982 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Job Opportunity Bulleting, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Kerlinger, Fred N., 1984 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Leadership Campaign, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Montalto, Laurence - DEG's Doctoral Student, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - OMAN, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Pace University, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Para Educator Center, 1976-1983 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Para Educator Center Board of Directors, 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Payne Fund, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - C.W. Post, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Preservice Teacher Education Committee, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Puerto Rico: Photos, Leases, InterAmerican University, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Sesquicentennial, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Student Activities, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Student Records - Stella Kaisted SEHNAP Recorder, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 182 2
  - Student Teaching, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Time Modules, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Virgin Islands Correspondence, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Visitors to SEHNAP and NYU, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Women's Studies Committee, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - SEHNAP Faculty Meetings, 1981-1983 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - SEHNAP Senate - Faculty Council - Standing Committees, 1980-1983 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Budget Advisory Committee, 1979-1983 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - SEHNAP Senate Meetings, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - MISSING INFO CHECK FOLDER (Box 13, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 183 0
  - Deans, Division Heads, Department Chairs Meetings, 1979-1982 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Dean Griffiths' Innovative Plans for the Schools - NYU Report, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Futures Report, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Mission Statements, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Goals Statement, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Future of the School Report, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Matrix for the Future of the School Report, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Transparencies from the Future of the School Report, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Plans for Alleviating Financial Problems of the Division of Education, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Undergraduate Concerns in SEHNAP, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Task Force on Graduate Student Recruitment, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Annual Report, 1978-1982 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Annual Report, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 184 8
  - Annual Report - Division of Education, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report - Division of Health, 1976-1977 (Box 14, File 3)
  - Annual Report - Division of Nursing, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Annual Report - Division of Arts and Arts Professions, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Other Programs, undated (Box 14, File 6)
  - Annual Report - School of Education, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Report to the Faculty, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - State of the School, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - State of the School Reports, 1967-1977 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Report to the Faculty, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - State of the School, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - State of the School, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - State of the School, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Transparencies for 9/25/78 State of the School Address to Faculty, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - State of the School, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Report to the Faculty, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Report to the Faculty, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Report to the Faculty (New Divisional Structure), 1965 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Notes for Faculty Talk, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Report to the Faculty, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Report to the Faculty, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - State of the School - W.A. Anderson, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Annual Report, 1959-1960 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Academic Affairs, 1980-1983 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 185 5
  - Commission on Academic Planning, 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Graduate Commission, 1979-1981 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Undergraduate Deans, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Undergraduate Education, Interschool Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - NYU Deans Council, 1977-1983 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Presidents Report to the Board of Trustees, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - SEHNAP Innovative Plans, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - President / Deans Weekly Meetings, 1981-1983 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - President Brademas' Inauguration, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Acting President Ivan Bennett, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Long Range Planning Report, President Sawhill, 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 186 3
  - NYU Annual Reports, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Sponsored Research Committee, 1981-1983 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - University Senate Meetings, 1981-1983 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Senate Financial Affairs, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Financial Planning Group (Budget Guidelines), 1984 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Art Therapy, Application for Approval, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - NY Board of Education Teacher Preparation Program, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Bermuda Training Institute, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - CADEA, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - CASDA, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Cleveland Conference, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Curriculum Research and Developmental Center in Mental Retardation, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Creative Leadership Award, 1978-1982 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 187 1
  - Land Grant - General, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Land Grant - Detroit, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Metro Center Advisory Board, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Development: Metro Center Proposals, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Metropolitan Center for Educational Research, Development and Training, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - NYS Council of University Deans, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Private Deans, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Spencer Deans, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Spencer Foundation, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - The United Airlines Foundation, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - UCEA Correspondence, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - UCEA Review, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Division of Health, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 188 9
  - Dept. of Occupational Health and Safety, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Dept. of Health Education, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - SIECUS, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Dept. of Occupational Therapy, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Dept. of Rehabilitation Counseling, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Program in Disability Determinations, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Dept. of Physical Therapy, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Division of Nursing, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - ICASA - International Center for Advanced Studies in Art, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Arts Administration Program, 1976 - 1983; 1980-1983 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Doctor of Arts, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Program in Technology and Industrial Education, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Dept. of Dance and Dance Education, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - 50 Years of Dance in Education, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Dept. of Music and Music Education, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Proposed School of Nursing, 1968-1974 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Nursing Education Faculty, 1971-1976 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Division of Nursing Faculty, 1971-1976 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Division of Nursing, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Dept. of Counselor Education, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 189 7
  - Dept. of Home Economics and Nutrition, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Program in Higher Education, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Annual Directory of Ongoing Research in Higher Education at NYU, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Review of Higher Education, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Program in Educational Sociology, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Program in Educational Administration, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Program in Interdisciplinary Studies, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Dept. of Organizational and Administrative Studies, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Dept. of Mathematics, Science and Statistics Education, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Program in Recreation and Leisure Stuides, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Program in Physical Education and Sports, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Division of Education, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence referred to DEG from Prof. Lonsdale's Office, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Curriculum Arts and Science, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Program in Educational Communication and Technology, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Graphic Arts Management and Technology, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Dept. of English, Speech, and Educational Theatre, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Dept. of Counselor Education, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Hoppock Resource Room Dedication, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Program in Philosophy of Education, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Program in History of Education, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Center for the Study of Food Service Management, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Dept. of Home Economics and Nutrition, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 190 5
  - Institute of Hebrew Culture and Education, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Educational Psychology, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Venezuela, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Dept. of Educational Psychology, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Psychology Doctorate, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Program in Bilingual Education, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Program in Secondary Education, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - International Education, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Center for Intercultural Studies, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Japanese Program in Bilingual and International Education, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Program in Foreign Languages, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Program in Business Education, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Program in Early Childhood and Elementary Education, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Dept. of Cultural Foundations, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Prog. In Religious Education, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Administration - Central, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 191 3
  - TECB - Teacher Education Conference Board, 1978-1983 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - SEHNAP - Alumni Fund Report, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 192 1
  - Sexuality and Disability, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - SCH ED. - Proposal for the Scholarship Program, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Humanities Council, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Hewlett Foundation, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Graduate Recruitment Inquiry Tracking System, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Conflict of Interest Disclosures, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Block Grants, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Gifts, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Committee to Study Improving the Efficiency of Operating the School, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - SCH ED. - Education Program Standing Committee of the Faculty Council, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - NYU - Newspaper Articles, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - SCH ED. - News Articles (from Lila Rosenblum), 1984 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - NYU - Post Articles, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Articles, Magazines, Newsletters, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - SEHNAP Faculty Council, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Teacher Corps: Project Roots, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Undergraduate Admissions, 1977-1982 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Reprographic Services, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Harris Surveys, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Mailings, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Wolanin, Thomas: Executive Asst. to the President, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Vandament, William: Sr. Vice President for Administration, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Kelly, Helen J., 1984 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Deans Group Weekly Reports, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - SEHNAP - Alternative Ed. D. Eval Committee, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - NYU - Development, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Development Programs, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Office of Correspondence, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Fontes, Honore, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 193 9
  - Meetings the Needs of Doctoral Education in New York State, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Deans Group Minutes & Agendas in Chronological Order, 1978 -1979 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Dean Joyce McGuinness - Weekly Reports, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Dean McGuinness - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Dean Joyce McGuinness, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Creative Arts Team - Theatre in Education Center, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Dean Elmer E. Baker, Jr., Vice Dean, Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 196 2
  - Dean Elmer E. Baker, Jr., Vice Dean, Weekly Reports, 1973-1978 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Dean Joyce McGuinnes, Asst. Dean for Adm. Services, Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Dean Arnold Spinner, Associate Dean for Research and Field Services, 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Baruch, Sylvia - Director of Academic Policy Development, Correspondence, 1974-1978 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Claxton, Allen E. - Vice President for Finance, 1976-1978 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Cott, Betty - VIce President for Public Affairs, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Goren, Allen E. - Vice President for Finance, 1976-1978 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Pizzoli, Lillian A. - Director of SEHNAP Budget, 1970-1978 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Sawhill, John C. - President, Correspondence, 1975-1979 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Sawhill, John C. - Replies Drafted or Written for Sawhill by Dean Griffiths, undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Athletics Subcommittee, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Computer Advisory Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Deans Group Agendum, 1976-1978 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Deans Group Minutes, undated (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1979-1981 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Financial Plan, Five Year, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 197 0
  - Fiscal Review, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Fiscal Review Reports, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Fiscal Review Group, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Funding Forecast, Facilities Plan and Capital, 1975-1980 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Integrated Core Curriculum, Ad Hoc Sub. Of Undergraduate Education Proj., 1978-1979 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Long Island Education Conference Board, undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Long Range Compensation Final Report, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - National Academy of Education, undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - President / Deans Meetings, 1977-1979 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - President / Deans Meetings, 1979-1981 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 198 8
  - Regents - The University of the State of New York, Board of, 1977-1980 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Regents - Federal Legislation and Education in New York State, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Regents - Tentative Statewide Plan for Development of Postsecondary Ed., 1976 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Senate Meetings (University), 1977-1981 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Senate - All-University Comm. on Student Evaluation to Undergrad Courses, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Senate Financial Affairs, 1977-1979 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Teacher Education Conference Board - General Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - TECD Meetings, 1979-1981 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 199 6
  - Accreditation, Puerto Rico, Institutional Report, 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Organization of the School of Education, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Administrative Organization, Job Description, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Advisory Council to the Puerto Rico Residence Center, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees, Puerto Rico Residence Center, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Community Education Program (Sobelman) Undergraduate Program, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Coordinated Liberal Studies, Commission on, 1971-1976 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Differential Tuition Plan, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - School of Education Faculty Seminar, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Fund Raising, undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Health Services, undated (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Infant and Toddler Program, undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Instructional Material Center, Bobst Library, undated (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - IYC - International Year of the Child, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Job Classification Study, 1978-1979 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - M.A. Degree, undated (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Master Plan Progress Report, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Model Cities, undated (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Memorial Services for John Collins Payne, undated (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Personnel Committee, undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 200 2
  - Personnel Services, 1974-1980 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Peru, Lima, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Piaget Manuscripts, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Project City Science, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Public Support of Education Conference, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Puerto Rico, Conservatory of Music, undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Puerto Rico Residence Center, Library, undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Off-Campus Programs, 1973-1979 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Off-Campus, Long Island Centers, 1976-1977 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Off-Campus, Briarcliff, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Recruitment, Part-Time Advertising Campaigns, undated (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Recruitment, School Case Statements and Policy Meetings, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Registration Improvement Program, undated (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Retired and Emeriti Professors, undated (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Space Charging, undated (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Sponsored Programs, undated (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Student Handbooks and Publications, 1972-1981 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - AACTE (American Assoc. of Colleges for Teacher Education), 1978 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 201 0
  - AASA (American Assoc. of School Administrators), 1971-1978 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - AERA (American Educational Research Assoc.), 1975-1978 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Board of Education, Board of Examiners, 1971-1978 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - AACUTE, 1970-1976 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - BEH (Bureau of Education for the Handicapped), Deans' Grant Project, 1976-1978 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - BEH Dean's Project - Mainstreaming, Conference in Minneapolis, 1976-1977 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Deans Network, 1976-1977 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - IIP (International Intervisitation Programme), 1974 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Fleischmann Report: Educators and Educational Policy, Chapter 13, undated (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Fleischmann Report: Teacher Demand and Supply Appendix 13A, undated (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - "Favoring Major Advances in Social Science", 1971 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Land Grant Deans Meeting, Colorado Springs, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Land Grant Winter Meeting, Detroit Plaza, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Land Grant Winter Executive Committee, St. Louis; Annual Fall Meeting, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Land Grant Winter Meeting, Dallas, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Land Grant Fall Meeting, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - New York State Deans, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - New York State Council of Deans, 1976-1978 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Regents New York City Project, 1977-1980 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 202 8
  - Rockefeller Fund, undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Research for Better Schools, Philadelphia, undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Spencer Proposals, 1980-1982 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Study Abroad, 1976-1981 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - UCEA COrrespondence, 1977-1981 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Urban Coalition, undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Attrition: Meetings with Departments, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - NYU Report on Rate of Graduation of Day Freshman who Entered in Fall, 1963-1969 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 203 6
  - NYU Report on the Survey of Transfer Undergraduate Students, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Budget Cost Accounting, 1972-1973 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Budget Projections (with transparencies), 1966 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Budget Estimate Worksheet, 1972-1973 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - NYU Financial Report, 1972-1973 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Budget Discussion with the President, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - SEHNAP Budget, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Budget: Capital Projects, 1977-1979 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Budget: Cost Allocation Procedure Review Committee, 1976-1979 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Cost Allocation Report, 1977-1978 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Budget: Cost Allocation Report, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Budget Advisory Committee, 1977-1979 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Budget Advisory Committee, General Background Statement, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Budget: Faculty Compensation Study, Summer Session, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Budget: Faculty Salaries, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Analysis of Income, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Expense Budget, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Recapitulation of Expense Budget by Activities, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Comparison of Budget, 1975-1977 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Budget Transparancies, undated (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Enrollment Data, 1972-1979 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Development Trip: Battlecreek, Chicago, Flint, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Development, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Graduate Planning, Commission on, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - School of Education All University Commission on Teacher Education, undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 204 4
  - Jane Maggin, undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Alex Rosen, undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - James Rutherford, Head, Division of Education, 1976-1977 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Richard Lonsdale, Head, Division of Education, 1977-1979 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Department of Communication Arts and Sciences, 1974-1978 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Department of Counselor Education, 1971-1979 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Department of Cultural Foundations, 1970-1978 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Program in History of Education, 1970-1978 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Program in Philosophy of Education, 1970-1976 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Program in Religious Education, 1971-1976 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Abraham Katsh Chair, 1971-1977 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Cyrus Gordon, Distinguished Professor, 1972-1978 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Department of Curriculum & Instruction, 1974-1978 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Department of Curriculum & Instruction Search for Chairperson, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Department of Early Childhood & Elementary Education, 1970-1974 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Department of Early Childhood & Elementary Education, 1974-1978 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Program in Communications in Eudcation, 1972-1978 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Program in Physical Education and Sports, 1977-1978 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 205 1
  - Program in Secondary Education, 1971-1978 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Program in Bilingual Education, 1977-1979 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - The Bilingual Review, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Program in Business Education, 1971-1978 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Program in Foreign Languages and International Education, 1971-1978 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Program in Foreign Languages and Bilingual Education, 1974-1976 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Languages, Teacher Education Program Proposal, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Department of Educational Psychology, 1976-1978 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Department of Home Economics and Nutrition, 1973-1978 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Center for the Study of Foodservice Management, 1977-1979 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Foodservice Management Conferences, 1976-1978 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Department of Leisure Studies, 1976-1979 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Department of Math, Science and Statistics Education, 1975-1979 (Box 35, Folder 14)